<Root>
	<!--GlossaryInstruction><![CDATA[Click any highlighted alphabet to view definitions of associated terms]]></GlossaryInstruction-->


 	<Letter Name="a">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>An Attorney</b> – An attorney is a person admitted to practice law in at least one jurisdiction to perform criminal and civil legal functions on behalf of clients.   
<b>Accounting or Accountancy</b> – Accounting basically is a service-based profession that provides reliable and relevant financial information, which is useful in making sound business decisions.
<b>Accrual Basis</b> – It is a method of accounting in which each item is entered as it is earned or incurred regardless of when actual payments are received or made. 
<b>Assets</b> – Assets acquired in operating activities are called revenues. 
<b>Advertising</b> – Advertising is a form of communication for marketing and used to encourage, persuade, or manipulate an audience (viewers, readers or listeners; sometimes a specific group) to continue or take some new action.  
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter> 

	 
	<Letter Name="b">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Business Plans</b> – A business plan is an essential roadmap for business’ success. This living document outlines the route a company intends to take to grow revenues.
<b>Business Goals</b> – It is a mission statement company sets to achieve the goals during its time in operation.  
<b>Blogs</b> – Blogs are usually used by individuals to record their observations and experiences. 
<b>Brokers</b> – Brokers are third party distributors who often buy directly from the distributor or wholesaler and sell it to retailers or end users.  
<b>Business Licenses</b> – Business Licenses are permits issued by government agencies that allow individuals to conduct business.  
<b>Board of Equalization</b> – California collects California state sales and use tax, as well as fuel, alcohol, and tobacco taxes and fees that provide revenue for state government and essential funding for counties, cities, and special districts.
<b>Business Property Insurance</b> – It is a must to protect your company’s assets. It also protects commercial property from perils such as fire, burning, and theft. Business property insurance is a must to protect your company's assets.   
<b>Bank Reconciliation</b> – It is a process that explains the difference between the bank balance shown in company’s bank statement, as supplied by the bank, and the corresponding amount shown in the organization's own accounting records at a particular point in time. 
<b>Balance Sheet</b> – A balance statement of financial position is a summary of the financial balances of a company.  
<b>Bank Statement</b> – Bank statement is a list of all transactions which occurred during a particular period of time and impacted cash in bank account of business. Such a statement is prepared by the bank and is provided to the company owning the bank account. 
<b>Break-even Analysis</b> – It is a technique widely used by production management accountants. It is used to determine when your business will be able to cover all of its expenses and begin to make a profit. 
<b>Business Description</b> – Business description allows you to get your ideas, plans and visions down on paper before you go any further. It is important to have a thorough understanding of what your business is, and the direction that you intend it to follow. 
<b>Business Valuation</b> – It is a set of procedures used to estimate the economic value of an owner’s interest in a business. Valuation is used by financial market participants to determine the price they are willing to pay or receive to perfect a sale of a business. 
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter> 

	 
	<Letter Name="c">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Corporation</b> – It is a separate legal entity that has been incorporated through a legislative process established through legislation. 
<b>Consultant</b> – A consultant is a person who provides professional advice in specific area of specialization such as Computer Technology, Engineering, Technology, Mechanics, etc.     
<b>Competitor Analysis</b> – Competitor analysis in marketing and strategic management is an assessment of the strengths and weaknesses of current and potential competitors.  
<b>Chamber of Commerce</b> – It is a form of business network. It is also referred to as a board of trade. 
<b>Common Area Maintenance (CAM)</b> – A common area maintenance charge refers to the fees paid by tenants. Such fees are usually paid to the landlord to recompense operating, repairing and maintaining charges.    
<b>Creditor</b> - A creditor is a person, bank, and other enterprise that has lent money to another party. 
<b>Cash Basis Method</b> – The cash method of accounting records revenue when cash is received, and records expenses when cash is paid. 
<b>Cash Flow Statement</b> – Cash flow statement predicts company’s cash balances in the future.  
<b>Contributed Capital</b> – Contributed capital is a component of equity resulting from the contributions of the capital resources from the owners.  
<b>Cash Ledger</b> – It is an accounting book of prime entry listing all the transactions that impacted cash in bank and this book is prepared by the accountant. 
<b>Credit History</b> – A credit history shows an individual's past record of paying bills, loans, etc. It is also used to verify that they are financially responsible.    
<b>Collateral</b> – Collateral are those personal and business assets that can be sold to pay back the loan. Every loan program, even many microloan programs, requires at least some collateral to secure a loan. 
<b>Cash Flow </b> – Cash flow is the movement of money into or out of a business, project, or financial product. It is usually measured during a specified, limited period of time. 
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>



	<Letter Name="d">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>DBA (Doing Business As)</b> – It is a legal term used in United States of America. It is a fictions term used under which one can conduct business. It is not an actual name of the business one conducts or is responsible for.  
<b>Distribution</b>– Distribution is the way in which the equity is distributed amongst the various stock-holders. 
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>
	

	<Letter Name="e">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Entrepreneur</b> – Entrepreneur is a person who organizes and manages any enterprise, especially a business, usually with considerable initiative and risk.  
<b>External Communication</b> – It includes email, brochures, newsletters, posters, advertisements and other forms of multimedia marketing designed to attract customers, partners and suppliers to conduct profitable business transactions. 
<b>Excess Liability Coverage</b> – Excess liability is insurance coverage that typically provides coverage beyond that of an underlying policy such as an automobile or homeowner’s policy.  
<b>Equity</b> – Equity is what the company “owes” to the owners. If a company goes bankrupt, liabilities are paid off first to the creditors, while equity is the last to be distributed. 
<b>Expenses</b> – Assets used in the process of generating revenues are called expenses.    
<b>Earnings before Income Tax</b> – It is an indicator of a company’s profitability, calculated as net income minus interest and tax.   
<b>E-Mail Marketing</b> – Email marketing is directly marketing a commercial message to a group of people using email. Every email sent to a potential or current customer could be considered email marketing. 
<b>Executive Summary</b> – It is a regular exercise in corporate world of giving executives a concise outline of the main points in a report, indicting where in the report look for detailed information.  
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter> 


	<Letter Name="f">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Federal Licenses and Permits</b> – If your business is regulated by federal government, you may need to obtain a federal license.  
<b>Financial Accounting</b> – A field of accounting that treats money as a means of measuring economic performance instead of as a factor of production.  
<b>Financial Statement</b> – A financial statement is a formal record of the financial activities of a business, person, or other entity.  
<b>Financial Reporting</b> – Financial reporting is a process through which companies communicate information to the public. 
<b>Fixed (overhead) expenses</b> – A fixed (overhead) cost refers to a specific type or group of business expenses. The word overhead in business is used to describe the cost of doing business or the amount of money an individual or company must spend in order to run and maintain a functional business. 
<b>Forecasts</b> – It is also referred to as forecasting. It is the process of making statements about events whose actual outcomes (typically) have not yet been observed. 
<b>Franchising</b> – Franchising is the practice of using another firm's successful business model. 
]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter> 


	<Letter Name="g">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>General Partnership</b> – Each of the two or partners will have unlimited liability for the debts of the business.   
<b>Gross Margin</b> – Gross margin ratio is the ratio of a business to its revenue. It is a profitability measuring what proportion of revenue is converted into gross profits.  
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="h">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="i">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Internal Communication</b> – It is the function responsible for effective communication or trade among participants within an organization, including states. 
<b>Investor</b> – An investor is an individual who commits money to investment products with the expectation of financial return.
<b>Income Statement</b> – It is company’s financial performance measured for over a certain period of time.  
<b>Income Tax</b> – Tax directly levied on an individual’s company or company’s income is called Income Tax.  
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="j">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>

	<Letter Name="k">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="l">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Limited Partnership</b> – Two or more partners unite to conduct a business. 
<b>Limited Liability</b> – It is a concept through which person's liability is limited to a fixed value of a person's investment in a company.  
<b>Liability</b> – A liability is defined as an obligation of an entity arising from past transactions or events, the settlement of which may result in the transfer or use of assets, provision of services or other yielding of economic benefits in the future.  
<b>Local Licenses and Permits</b> –It is an agreement between government and an entrepreneur which requires an entrepreneur to comply with the local, state and federal laws in order to conduct businesses in a specific territory.      
<b>Liability Insurance</b> – Insurance that protects a company and the owner of the company in the event of a formal lawsuit or other third party claim.   
<b>Life Insurance</b> –The term, ‘Life Insurance’ is an assurance of an individual’s life in the event of untimely death.  It provides coverage at fixed rate of payments for a limited period of time. 
<b>Loan Proposal</b> – Loan proposal is usually prepared and presented by bank’s officer. 
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="m">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Managerial Accounting</b> – It involves preparing and providing timely financial and statistical information to business managers so that they can make day-to-day and short-term managerial decisions. 
<b>Management Profile</b> – It is a detailed description about the company’s owner, board of directors and the products/services company renders to its clients.   
<b>Marketing  Information</b> – A system that analyzes and assesses marketing information, gathered continuously from sources inside and outside an organization.
<b>Marketing</b> – Marketing is the way companies interact with consumers to create relationships that are beneficial to both parties. 
<b>Market Strategy</b> – A well-crafted marketing strategy identifies customer groups which a particular business can serve better than its target competitors.  
<b>Marketing Plans</b> – Marketing plans is a well written, comprehensive marketing plan, which is the focal point of all business ventures. It describes how you plan to attract and retain customers - the most crucial aspect of a business. 
<b>Marketing Mix</b> – It is combination of the 4 P's of Marketing. It is the combination of product, price, place (distribution), and promotion. It is used in marketing by marketing professionals.  
<b>Media Relations</b> – It involves working with media enterprises to promote about products, company and the new launch.  
<b>Marketing Analysis</b> – A market analysis studies the attractiveness and the dynamics of a special market within a special industry.
]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="n">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>NNN (Triple Net Lease)</b> – A lease agreement that designates the lessee (the tenant) as being solely responsible for all of the costs relating to the asset being leased in addition to the rent.  
<b>Net loss</b> – Net loss is the opposite of the net income. Net loss results from the excess of asset decreases (expenses) the over asset increases (revenues) for a period. 
<b>Networking</b> – Business networking is a socioeconomic activity by which groups of like-minded business people recognize, create, or act upon business opportunities. 
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>



	<Letter Name="o">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Outreach</b> – Outreach is an activity of providing services to populations who might not otherwise have access to those services. 
<b>Overhead Expenses</b> – Overhead refers to all non-labor expenses required to operate your business.
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>



	<Letter Name="p">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Podcast</b> – A podcast is a type of digital media consisting of an episodic series of audio, video, PDF, or ePub files subscribed to and downloaded through streamed online to a computer or mobile device.
<b>Professional Advisor</b> – They closely work with individuals who are most likely to create personal, named funds at these public foundations.  
<b>Payroll Service Provider</b> – Payroll Service Providers allow small businesses to outsource complex payroll issues at very low costs.  
<b>Pension Plan Manager</b> – They (Pension scheme managers) are responsible for ensuring that pension schemes operate effectively and sustainably.  
<b>Pre-employment Screening Service</b> – This service helps to check and verify the background of an employee to be recruited.  
<b>Permits</b> – It allows/permits someone to do something within the legal norms.    
]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>



	<Letter Name="q">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>

	<Letter Name="r">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Retained Earnings</b> – It refers to the sum of net income which is retained by the company rather than distributed to its owners as share.   
<b>Revenue</b> – It is income that a company receives from its business operations such as business activities, usually from the sale of goods and services to customers.  
<b>Reality Checks</b> - An assessment to determine if one's circumstances or expectations conform to reality.
]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>

	<Letter Name="s">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Software</b> – Software is any set of machine-readable instructions that directs a computer's processor to perform specific operations. 
<b>Strategic Technology Plan</b> – It is a specific type of strategy plan that lets an organization know where they are and where they want to be sometime in future in regards of technology and infrastructure. 
<b>Sole Proprietorship</b> – It is a type of business entity that is owned and run by an individual.   
<b>"S" Corporation</b> – It is corporation that makes a valid election to be taxed under subchapter S chapter 1 of the Internal Revenue Code.  
<b>State Licenses and Permits</b> – The state in which you propose to conduct business may require you to have special licenses and permits to do business.   
<b>The Seller’s Permit</b> – A seller’s permit allows you to collect sale taxes from customers and your clients, which you in turn pay to the state, local or federal government.  
<b>Start up Cost</b> – The required amount of money to set up a new business. 
<b>SBS Loan</b> – Loans provided to small businesses for various purposes by a lender. These loans may have less restrictive requirements, enabling the small business to secure the funds. 
<b>Strategic Planning</b> – Strategic planning is an organization's process of defining its strategy, or direction, and making decisions on allocating its resources to pursue this strategy.  
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>

	<Letter Name="t">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Trademark</b> – It is a brand name or sign, or symbol which represents a particular name, source or company. 
<b>Tradeshow Marketing</b> –Tradeshow Marketing is large exposition to promote awareness and sales of especially new products within an industry.  
]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>

	<Letter Name="u">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>



	<Letter Name="v">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Veto</b> - It is the power of an officer of the state to officially stop the unilaterally a piece of legislation. 
<b>Variable (related to business sales) Expenses</b> - Variable costs are directly related to business sale. They change with the volume of the product you sell.  
]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="w">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[<b>Workers Compensation Insurance</b> - It helps protect your employees from injuries in the course of employment and keeps you in compliance with workers compensation laws.]]></Text>
			
		</Word>
	</Letter>


	<Letter Name="x">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>

	<Letter Name="y">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>

	<Letter Name="z">
		<Word>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
			<Text><![CDATA[]]></Text>
		</Word>
	</Letter>
</Root>